Next, we will talk about how to do the round-shaped processing of the front part of the round shape.
We all know that there are more A, B, C, D, E, F in the round shape,
so it will be more complicated when we actually make it.
Our A-shape and X-shape are all sawn.
In order to make our production more simple, we can combine all A-shape and B-shape.
In 3D, the round-shaped processing is relatively simple.
We use the editor's dot-and-line tool,
press the Shift key to select the two edges of the A-shape,
press the right mouse button, and select Cut.
At this point, we will cut this shape and delete it.
After deleting it, press the Shift key to select the original shape edge of the A-shape,
press the Shift key to select the original shape edge of the A-shape,
and press a button to merge it.
In this way, we can see that the volume of the round shape will increase,
and the volume will merge with the A-shape.
Similarly, let us do the same for the B-shape.
Press the Shift key to select the two edges of the A-shape,
press the right mouse button, release the Shift key to select the A-shape,
press the right mouse button, and then select Cut.
After you cut, you can delete this part in the middle,
and after deleting it, change to the edit and line tool,
press the Shift key and then the left mouse button,
and connect the two edges of the B-thread with the right-click key.
After we've done this,
because the board is not symmetrical,
we need to do it again.
Now we've completed the process of removing the A-thread and moving it to the C-thread.
We only need to keep the C-thread.